

Nicholas Brown Curriculum Vitae

Nick has build two houses with his father and renovated three more. He's spent half a year camping around Australia and he's lived in Japan. Recently he attended an Artificial Intelligence workshop in San Fran and completed a web-development internship in Melbourne.

He has an insatiable book appetite. He cares deeply about those around him. His friends enjoy his company and banter. He has built a computer from the ground up. He manages the website for his family's Wine Tours business.

During his science degree, he founded the Anu Rationality Society, and served as a board member and volunteer for the Effective Altruism Society.

Nick is driven, thoughtful and resilient. His curiosity drives him to understand how the world works. He was School Captain of his high school, Mt Carmel. He plays guitar and likes to sketch.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Birth September 6, 1995

Address Unit 2, 20 Oliver St, Lyneham, ACT

Phone 0467903638

Mail nickaustinbrown at gmail

EDUCATION

B.Sc, Computer Science and Mathematics 2014-2018

Australian National University

Japan Exchange 2015

Osaka University

Workshop on AI Safety May 2016

Centre for Applied Rationality, San Francisco

Astronomy Winter School May 2015

Reasearch School of Anstronomy and Astrophysics

Anu Secondary College

Physics

The Tournament of the Towns

Intensive Mathematics Competition

Daramarlan College 2012-2014

WORK EXPERIENCE

Effective Altruism Anu 2017-2018

General Committee Member

Rationality Anu 2016-2018

Founder, Treasurer

MentorLoop Internship 2018-

Backend Web-Development

SKILLS

Languages Python, LATEX, Java, Haskel, Lisp

Hobbies Bouldering, books, meta-cognition, swing dancing

REFERENCES

S. Petocz 6125 3280 simon.petocz@anu.edu.au R. Cooper 0447372662 randbcooper@gmail.com

J. Mettes u5334216@anu.edu.au